<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Visual Computing</title><link>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/</link><description>Recent content on Visual Computing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/3dBrushBased/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/3dBrushBased/</guid><description>3D Brush Based using a Camera # Introduction # The feasibility of using the camera was investigated using the handpose ml5 library to simulate a 3d brush.
Methods # To obtain the depth value using the hand we use the ml5 handpose library that provides us with 20 points along the hand
Then, to optimize the performance we only use the central point of the hand, corresponding to the one located at the knuckle of the middle finger.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/blindness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/blindness/</guid><description>Color blindness # Problem statement # People with colour vision deficiency find it difficult to identify and distinguish between certain colours.
Colour vision deficiency is not usually anything to be concerned about.
Most people get used to it over time, it will not normally get any worse, and it&amp;rsquo;s rarely a sign of anything serious.
But it can sometimes cause issues such as:
Difficulty at school if colours are used to help with learning Problems with food, such as identifying whether meat is fully cooked or whether fruit is ripe Getting medications confused if they&amp;rsquo;re not clearly labelled Trouble identifying safety warnings or signs Slightly limited career choices – certain jobs, such as pilots, train drivers, electricians and air traffic controllers, may require accurate colour recognition Background # Definition # Color blindness is a reduced ability to distinguish between color when compared to the standard for normal human color vision.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/log/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/log/</guid><description>Logs # March 29th Platonic solid Textured
TextureMode(Normal)
Ishihara Test
Change Image Colors Palette from a diagnostic
May 5th Rendering - Rasterization
Antialiasing implementation for a triangle using barycentric coordinates.
Scene Trees - Main Spaces
Implementation of a 3D brush using the ml5.js library.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/mainSpaces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/mainSpaces/</guid><description>Main Spaces # treeLocation SCREEN to WORLD // Goal in the 3d Brush is double, to implement: // 1. a gesture parser to deal with depth, i.e., // replace the depth slider with somehing really // meaningful. You may use a 3d sensor hardware // such as: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leap_Motion // or machine learning software to parse hand (or // body) gestures from a (video) / image, such as: // https://ml5js.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/Rasterization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/Rasterization/</guid><description>Rasterization # #antialiasing { margin: 20px; border: solid 0.5px; border-radius: 5px } .img-right{ width: 120px; float: right; margin: 0px 20px; } Problem statement # What we do with the rasterization process is breaking down a continuous surface (the triangle) into discrete elements (the pixels). The problem is similar to trying to represent a continuous curve or surface with Lego bricks. And the solution to this problem in rendering is called anti-aliasing, that will be implemented using the barycentric coordinates.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/solids/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://AlejandroUN.github.io/docs/shortcodes/solids/</guid><description>Platonic Solids # A platonic solid is a polyhedron all of whose faces are congruent regular polygons, and where the same number of faces meet at every vertex. More
Tetrahedron # " --</description></item></channel></rss>